[{"answer": "It did, but, you know, it's about to land bashing (ph) for running a terrible system.", "docId": "131029pmt", "aSentId": 28, "question": "It kind of took the wind out of your sails, didn't it?", "qSentId": 27}, {"answer": "They said that about everything.", "docId": "131029pmt", "aSentId": 33, "question": "Some of the last two weeks, I mean has it been as I said a comedian's dream this?", "qSentId": 32}, {"answer": "Well, I think the country in general is on a decline.", "docId": "131029pmt", "aSentId": 43, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 42}, {"answer": "You know, I'm not a big fan of scapegoating.", "docId": "131029pmt", "aSentId": 143, "question": "I mean she's somebody carry the can for the fact the system has started so badly?", "qSentId": 142}, {"answer": "Well, no.", "docId": "131029pmt", "aSentId": 145, "question": "Ever?", "qSentId": 144}, {"answer": "But when she says we're going to be bring in the A-Team.", "docId": "131029pmt", "aSentId": 157, "question": "Why get rid of her now to make it -- make the situation worst?", "qSentId": 156}, {"answer": "Oh, I know.", "docId": "131029pmt", "aSentId": 159, "question": "Hang on a second, she's the president's great initiative?", "qSentId": 158}, {"answer": "That's actually true.", "docId": "131029pmt", "aSentId": 163, "question": "... before?", "qSentId": 162}, {"answer": "Not credible and not excusable.", "docId": "131029pmt", "aSentId": 172, "question": "Is he really credible that the President whose massive legacy maybe based around this, didn't know anything about anything problematic?", "qSentId": 171}, {"answer": "I've actually never seen one.", "docId": "131029pmt", "aSentId": 204, "question": "Just to clarify you don't like cat videos, right?", "qSentId": 203}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "131029pmt", "aSentId": 282, "question": "Genuine whistleblower?", "qSentId": 281}, {"answer": "I think so.", "docId": "131029pmt", "aSentId": 285, "question": "No concerns?", "qSentId": 284}, {"answer": "What we really don't want is a rogue agency.", "docId": "131029pmt", "aSentId": 315, "question": "What is the line?", "qSentId": 314}, {"answer": "Well, because I think for one, we don't care to learn about other countries.", "docId": "131029pmt", "aSentId": 347, "question": "Why is that?", "qSentId": 346}, {"answer": "Yeah, (inaudible) the face off you.", "docId": "131029pmt", "aSentId": 409, "question": "I read -- now this week it was two stories in the news and had to do with race, the Julianne, how -- is that how you pronounce that?", "qSentId": 408}, {"answer": "It's always perfect -- perfectly wrong, you know.", "docId": "131029pmt", "aSentId": 428, "question": "What you make in her argument?", "qSentId": 427}, {"answer": "It probably will be.", "docId": "131029pmt", "aSentId": 457, "question": "Could it be him against Chris Christie?", "qSentId": 456}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "131029pmt", "aSentId": 470, "question": "You mean oversees, what are they saying about him?", "qSentId": 469}, {"answer": "You know, we don't know until he -- if he became president.", "docId": "131029pmt", "aSentId": 472, "question": "What would it mean for America and for America's reputations, you think?", "qSentId": 471}, {"answer": "Probably not in my lifetime.", "docId": "131029pmt", "aSentId": 504, "question": "Will it ever change?", "qSentId": 503}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "131029pmt", "aSentId": 507, "question": "Less people have more guns, isn't that right?", "qSentId": 506}, {"answer": "Absolutely, I mean that's what happens when the tipping point is reached with the states, I think that's what would happen with gay marriage and probably some day with marijuana itself.", "docId": "131029pmt", "aSentId": 567, "question": "And will just a federal law encompassing the whole of America?", "qSentId": 566}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "131029pmt", "aSentId": 595, "question": "You're asking me to choose between my children?", "qSentId": 594}, {"answer": "George Carlin did.", "docId": "131029pmt", "aSentId": 607, "question": "Will you literally do stand up until the day they carry you out in a box?", "qSentId": 606}, {"answer": "It would be a great way to go.", "docId": "131029pmt", "aSentId": 610, "question": "Will that be your dream exit from life?", "qSentId": 609}, {"answer": "Well, I'm hoping Reichert Well (ph) is correct and I'll live forever because, you know, he says that what he calls the singularity that's coming in the year 2029 points out that we're already partly machine, people have all kinds of stents and artificial hearts.", "docId": "131029pmt", "aSentId": 618, "question": "Truthfully you want to live to be 100?", "qSentId": 617}, {"answer": "AHER: Well, it does matter because when we didn't use to have this kind of places where you could retreat to your, you know, (inaudible) of thinking, public discourse was the better for it because you had to hear a conflicting idea, now you don't.", "docId": "131029pmt", "aSentId": 652, "question": "Does it matter?", "qSentId": 651}, {"answer": "That doesn't get him staying, nothing will.", "docId": "131029pmt", "aSentId": 667, "question": "Wrestling?", "qSentId": 666}, {"answer": "I like Jay Leno.", "docId": "131029pmt", "aSentId": 686, "question": "What do you make of Jay Leno?", "qSentId": 685}, {"answer": "Oh, well, of course a lot of it is that.", "docId": "131029pmt", "aSentId": 690, "question": "Is it jealousy?", "qSentId": 689}, {"answer": "He doesn't have someone talking in the ear of the network executive like the other guys do saying, get rid of Jay, he's too old.", "docId": "131029pmt", "aSentId": 705, "question": "He does himself right?", "qSentId": 704}, {"answer": "... so he would listen -- of course.", "docId": "131029pmt", "aSentId": 711, "question": "Do you have an agent?", "qSentId": 710}]